A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1
  - Crete, 1/807
    - "WHDIC-Sanitation Malaria Control-DDT Residual Spraying-Island of Crete-Region K." Map of pesticide spraying., 1947; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 4, Folder 5)
      807 M1
  - Cyprus, 1/809
    - Survey of Cyprus Administration Map., 1935; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 4)
      M-P 809
  - Egypt, 1/812
    - Map 1: "Drakat (zones) in which An. Gambiae was present in the month of 1945 January", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 4, Folder 5)
      812 M9
    - Map 2, "Drakat (zones) in which An. Gambiae was present in the month of 1945 February." Gambiae eradication map. Ministry of Public Health, Egypt. (Ministry of Public Health, Egypt)., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 4, Folder 5)
      812 M10
    - "Railway map of the delta and fyun, " laminated. Printed by Survey of Egypt., 1926, revised: 1930; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 4, Folder 5)
      Ba-1
  - Lebanon, 1/833
    - "The American University of Beirut." Blueprints of university grounds, buildings, etc., 1927 April; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 12) (Drawer B 4, Folder 6)
      P-MsAm3a
    - "Mortuary & Pathology Building," American University of Beirut., 1924 November 3; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 6) (Drawer B 4, Folder 6)
      P-msAm3p #1-6
    - "Mary Bliss Dale Home for Pupil Nurses:" American University of Beirut., ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer B 4, Folder 6)
      P-msAm3m
    - "Hospital Development Plans:" American University of Beirut Hospital., BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 4, Folder 6)
      P-msAm3e #1&2
  - Program and Policy, 1/900
    - R.F. Paris architectural drawings-IEB, 1955; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 11) (Drawer A 2, Folder 1)
    - map of Rockefeller Foundation in Paris I.E.B, MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer A 2, Folder 1)
    - R.F Paris Office I.E.B., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 2, Folder 1)
    - building plan of 54th Floor, showing leasees, 1956 August 29; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1.2
    - Aspen Music Festival 40th Season Poster, 1988; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
      Oversized material, not microfilmed, 1960-1981
    - New York City Charter Revision Commission Poster, 1988; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Carver Community Cultural Center Poster. Carnegie Institute of Washington. Poster for Texas theatre., 1988-1989; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Awards for Excellence: "Program for the Production of Low-Income Housing" From the Fannie Mae Foundation, 1989; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Map of Jackson, MS., 1989; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Federal Laws and Regulations Prohibiting Sex Discrimination in Educational Institutions". From Association of American Colleges., 1990; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Kids Count" Chart from Casey Foundation, 1990; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Easy Does It- League of Women Voters Education Fund Registration and Absentee Voting Procedures by State", 1985; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Dawn of the Information Age, 1990; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Poster for the Zone Theater of the Visuals Adaptation of Kandinsky's "The Yellow Sound", 1980; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Poster for "Exotic Events Times Square Show". Signed by William R. Stephens., 1980; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - H.H. The Dalai Lama Kalachakra Initiation Poster. Signed by X Bryant, 1981; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Hycanthone Timeline" from the Center for Public Resources Pharmaceutical Conference., 1981; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - The Aspen Musical Festival 32nd Season Poster., 1981; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Agricultural Land Datasheet." From the International Grasslands Congress., 1981; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Map of Thailand and Bangkok. From Richard W. Lyman., POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
      100
    - Poster- "The American Hero- Myths and Media". For the Sun Valley Center., 1979; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "The Rider and the West". From the Sun Valley Center., 1979; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Alphabets" Exhibit Announcement by Joseph Reed. Wesleyan University., 1978; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Highlands Highlights Newsletter," Vol. 7, No. 6, 1967. From the Southern Highland Handicraft Guild., PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Highlands Highlights Newsletter," Vol. 11, No. 11, 1971. From the Southern Highland Handicraft Guild., PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Seven Things Nonprofits can Learn from Profits." From the Taft Corporation,., 1977; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Annual Chicano Film Festival., 1977; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Annual Chicano Film Festival. From Oblate College of the Southwest., 1976; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Cross-World Food Puzzle, from OxFam America., 1977; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Open Plan 77." From the Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies, 1978; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Map of Alaska, 1977; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - Ad from the Wolf Trap Farm for Performing Arts., 1977; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - "Regional Issues 1977: Are Circumstances Beyond Our Control." From the Association of Bay Area Governments., POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 1)
    - 2 series of maps from the Rice Center for Community Design for the Texas Gulf Coast Program., 1976; MAP (Quantity 14) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "The Festival of Women's Films." At Fifth Avenue Cinema, 1976; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Proposed Laboratory for Biotechnological Research, University of Denver." From Denver Research Institute., 1959 September 28; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Inter-American Seminar." From International Seminars incorporated., 1958; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - drawings of New Facilities: "At the Institute for Experimental Pathology.", 1958; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      715
    - Central Medical Library, Kyoto University, 1958; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      609
    - "Juan Downey Energy System." Exhibit at Center for Inter-American Relations, 1975; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Seasonal Climates of the Tropical and Sub-Tropical Zones," from the Agency for International Development., 1973; (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Soday Research Foundation Project #777." From the Soday Research Foundation, 1975; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Comp You Ter," from the National Student Computer Fair, 1975; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Dow Jones Industrial Average of Stock Prices Chart, 1973; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "National Conferences on Rural America Program," in Washington D.C., 1975 April; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "The Shoup Voting Machine Electomap," from the Government Affairs Institute, 1958; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Here are some people we met this summer. They are trying to save your country's history." Newspaper Poster. From the America the Beautiful Fund, 1973; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "1976 World Amnesty Year for Writers in Prison," from P.E.N, 1975; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      103
    - International Conference on Global Water Law Systems, 1975; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Show bill for the Guthrie Theater, 1974; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "The Politics of Culture," from P.E.N., 1974; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Writers in Prison", P.E.N., 1973, 1974; POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Dormitory, Cafeteria, Recreation Center," from the Asian Vegetable Development Center, 1972; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      605
    - Map of the Toronto waterfront, 1972; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      427
    - Draft sheet illustration of the Roman Forum, from G.C. Izenour, 1972; RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Specimen map from the Pine Creek Study, Penn State, 1972; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Poster of speech: "The Holy Name: Address Delivered by William J. McCormick?", 1972; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Floor plan from the Japan Women's University Library, 1963; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Section of the Sunday Magazine newspaper: "The Bangkok Post." 4 pages, 1970; PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      617
    - Map: "Properties to be acquired for Indiana Harbor Project No. 1," from Purdue-Calumet Development Foundation, 1968; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Map 2: "Urban Renewal Plan for Indiana Harbor," from P-CDF, 1968; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Poster for New York Pro Musica production of "An Entertainment for Elizabeth", 1969; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Two copies of floor plan from Temple B'nai Abraham, from the Urban Communications Institute, 1970; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Poster for "The Hotel: A Play," from Columbia College Theatre Center., 1971; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Poster for "Fanshen," Columbia College Theatre Center, 1971; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Poster for the "Chicago Project", from Columbia College, 1971; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Poster for the "Free Theatre Improvisational Ensemble, Columbia College, 1971; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Proposed Timeline for New Career Development Program for Elementary School Principals in Metropolitan Areas," from Columbia University, 1969; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Mailer for the Inner-City Repertory Company, 1970; PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Promotional Poster for the Actor's Theatre of Louisville, 1970; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Map of New York City: "Areas for Redevelopment and Relocation," from Robert Moses, 1968; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Blueprint: "Indiana Institute of Technology, Ground Floor.", 1966; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      323
    - Blueprint: "National School of Agriculture, ITT Library.", 1966; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - NS of A, Suggested Furniture Layout, First Floor., 1966; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - NS of A, Suggested Furniture Layout, Second Floor., 1966; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Area du Pesquisas Ecologicas Do Guama, Belem-Para-Brasil," from the Guama Ecological Research Area, 1966; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "Improvement of Cafeteria and Dormitory Management, University of the Philippines.", 1964; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      242 D
    - National Institute of Agricultural Technology., 1963; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 6) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      301
    - Page from Financial Times: "Ceylon: A Financial Times Survey." Pages 7-14, 1967 June 5; PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      401
    - Pages 9-12 of the Hindustan Times, Advertisers Announcement from the National Seed Corporation., 1967; PUBLICATION (Quantity 5) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Doshisha University, 1961; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - elevations and floorplans for the National School of Agriculture Library, Mexico, 1966; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - Indian Council of Agricultural Research, Rice., 1967; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
    - "U.P. Dilliman Cottage, No. 1402," from Administration, 1964; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      242
    - Mailer from the Latin American Association of Plant Science, 1967; PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
      300
    - 2 site plans from the University Medical Sciences Library, 1963; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 11, Folder 2)
  - China Medical Board: PUMC, 1.4
    - Personnel record of officers of RF, CMB, and PUMC, including dates of services, 1913-1950; DOCUMENT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 2)
    - "Bus Map of Peking, smuggled out of China by Stephen Chang." Double-sided. Mailed to Mary E. Ferguson., 1965 July 28; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 2)
    - "Map and Guide of Peking." Japan Tourist Bureau, Tokyo. From JDR, Jr.'s trip to Peking in 1921., 1920s; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 3)
  - International Health Board/Division, 1.5
    - Charts and Graphs related to work in China., VARIOUS (Quantity 16) (Drawer A 12, Folder 5)
      RF RG 5 - IHB, SERIES 3 - REPORTS, 601 CHINA
      SEPARATED FROM PAPER COLLECTION
    - Annotated map of Pike County, Alabama (5 copies.), 1921; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer A 12, Folder 7)
      RF RG 5 IHB, SERIES 3 REPORTS, SUBSERIES 2 ALABAMA
    - Map of Baldwin County, Alabama., 1921; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 12, Folder 7)
    - Annotated map of Sumter County, Alabama., 1921; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 12, Folder 7)
    - Annotated map of Pike County, Alabama., 1921; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 12, Folder 7)
    - large color map of Tokyo (?), 1924; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 5, Folder 4)
      back is marked: "609 J"; front is marked "M 609 T57 b"; pencil description on back of map: "Heiser & Grant: pertinent data relating to General Public Health Survey of Japan 1924 May 12-June 25"
      Separated from RG 5, Series 2.
    - large color map of Tokyo (?), 1924; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 5, Folder 4)
      back is marked: "609 J"; front is marked "M 609 T57 b"; pencil description on back of map: "Heiser & Grant: pertinent data relating to General Public Health Survey of Japan, 1925 May 12-June 25"
    - black and white printed map with hand-drawings and key to indicate location of parasites, in red ink, 1924; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 5, Folder 4)
      back is marked "462H"; front is marked "462 M34"; pencil description on back of map: "Hookworm Infection in Ceylon-J. Frank Doherty 1925"
    - color map of Georgia, with some notations in marker, copyright 1918; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 5, Folder 4)
      back is marked "212"; pencil description on back: "Report of Dr. Frederick H Bailey (or Busby?) to Dr. John A Ferrell regarding Georgia State Board of Health"
    - color map printed on mylar titled "Swamp Areas in Palestine, as reviewed by the Anti-Malarial Advisory Commission", 1924; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer A 5, Folder 4)
      back is marked "825 I", "A22"; back is marked "825 M2; pencil description on back: "Field Studies in Malaria in Palestine-Paul S. Carley"
    - small posters and flyers about seeking medical care for venereal diseases and syphillis, from the Department of Public Sanitation (in Spanish), POSTER (Quantity 5) (Drawer J 3, Folder 3)
    - 3 maps of health stations in southeastern France, relating to the TB campaign, with notations (Department de l'Herault), 1929 ?; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
      marked "500 M28", "500 M29", "500 M30"
    - 2 large posters advocating for vaccination, part of TB campaign in France, 1929; POSTER (Quantity 2) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
    - chart of mortality rates, from Spain, 1929 ?; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
    - map of Provincia de Caceras "distribution of gambusias", with some notations, 1929; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
      marked "795 M32"
    - 7 signs supporting hygiene, dental health, and vaccination, in French, POSTER (Quantity 8) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
    - large page advertising a child health organization, with illustrations of healthy activities, POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
    - 2 small maps of health stations in France, "Department de Seine-et-Marne", 1927; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
      marked "500 M31" and "500 M32"
    - 5 small sheets with statistics about health stations in Seine and Marne, 1925, 1926; GRAPH (Quantity 5) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
    - 4 maps of health stations in Petritch, Bulgaria, divided into zones, 1929; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer J 3, Folder 4)
      marked "711 M8 - 12" and "805 M12"
    - 2 maps of health stations in Petritch, Bulgaria, divided into zones, 1929; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer Q 4, Folder 7)
    - 3 maps of health stations in Petritch, Bulgaria, MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer Q 4, Folder 7)
      marked "711 M5-M7"
- Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller, 2
  - Pocantico Hills-road between private road and Sleepy Hollow Road (34 cop.2) (W. Kidde), 1928 May; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 85)
  - Road map of the estate of Mr. John D. Rockefeller Jr. at Pocantico Hills, NY-General, New House & Gardens-Atterbury, Grosvenor-House. Construction, 1928-1934; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 85)
  - Campus of RIMR - Showing Parcels of Land Contributed by the Messrs. Rockefeller, 1931; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 91)
  - Diagram of Malt Property, 66-64 Sts. Ave. A and East River- 4 filed extra copy- red shows property leased from city to Eufur Mortgage Co. 31.10- Malt EM #2 (Wm. A. White & Sons), 1922 November 20; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 91)
    marked 31.10 on back
  - proposed layout of parcels of land (G. Knocne), 1903 May; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 1, Folder 91)
    #3- 31.10 RIMR
  - "Survey of Property prepared for John D. Rockefeller, Jr." (with duplicate), 1942 May 4; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 8, Folder 1)
    TX-EX; P.H89-A
  - Pocantico Hills-General, New House & Gardens-Plat of-Aspinwall Lane, 1912. (Drawer C 2, Folder 5)
  - Declaration of the New York State Society of the Cincinnati naming James Stephen Van Cortland as a member of the society., 1885 July 4; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 7, Folder 14)
    V2315
  - The Archaeological Society of Athens; diploma bestowed upon JDR Jr. as honorary member. Athens., 1956 July 23; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 1)
  - Formal Letter from the Holland Society of New York to John D. Rockefeller Jr. Commemorating JDR Jr's contributions to Sleepy Hollow., 1948 May 21; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 1)
  - Letter to JDR JR. from the Union Church of Pocantico Hills thanking him for his patronage., 1957 October; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 1)
  - Greek Archaeological Society in Athens Certificate of Honorary Membership bestowed upon JDR Jr., 1938 October 23; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of bronze plate commemorating the donation of vessels to the U.S. Navy for the war effort by JDR JR. Accompanying letter is dated May 4, 1921, signed by Winthrop W. Aldrich., PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 2)
  - Certification from the American Museum of Natural History certifying JDR Jr., as patron of the museum. (Made by Tiffany and Company), 1902 February 10; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 2)
  - Certificate from the American Museum of Natural History certifying JDR Jr. as associate benefactor. (Made by Tiffany and Company), 1922 February 6; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 2)
  - Certificate from the American Museum of Natural History certifying JDR Jr. as an endowment member. (Made by Tiffany and Company), 1926 January 4; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of the Albany Burgesses Core certifying JDR Jr. as a life member. Signed by Walter Reed., 1914 May 11; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 3)
  - Certificate of membership of JDR Jr. to the Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York., 1900 April 5; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 3)
  - Certificate of the Sisters of Mercy of the Province of New York declaring to their benefactor, JDR Jr., their foreface to God of prayer, labor, and sacrifice in the spiritual and corporal works of mercy., AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 3)
  - Resolution of the City Council of Cleveland Heights, Ohio accepting gift of land from JDR Jr. Bears seal of the City of Cleveland Heights, 1938 April 18; DOCUMENT (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 3)
  - Mounted photograph with accompanying description, "Regional Plan Award to John D. Rockefeller JR." Photograph depicts Liberty Island, Ellis Island, and Lower Manhattan from New York City Harbor., 1956 October 17; PHOTOGRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 3)
  - Certificate naming JDR Jr. as an Officer of the "Order National De la Legion D'Honneur"., 1921 August 25; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 4)
  - Certificate naming JDR Jr. as a Grand-officer of the "Ordre National De la Legion D'Honneur"., 1933 April 15; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 4)
  - Honorary Degree from the Free University of Brussels to John D. Rockefeller., 1930 June 23; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 4)
  - Resolution of the Board of Trustees of St. John's hospital, accepting JDR, Jr.'s gift to hospital., DOCUMENT (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 5)
  - Certificate electing JDR, Jr. as a "Patron of Exploration" of the Explorer's Club of New York., 1938 December 27; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 5)
  - Note thanking JDR, Jr. for his gift to the Board of Trustees of the General Education Board. Signatures of all members of GEB board., 1920 February 26; DOCUMENT (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 5)
  - JDR, Jr.'s copy of certificate he accepted on behalf of the Rockettes, from Count De FontNouvelle, French Consul-General at the Music Hall., 1957 November 25; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 5)
  - Award given to JDR, Jr. of the Friedsam Medal by the Architectural League., AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 5)
  - Gold Medal Award given to Rockefeller Center by 5th Ave. Association, Inc. at the recommendation of the Committee on Architectural Awards., 1939 February 7; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 5)
  - Formal Proclamation from the British Government bearing excerpts of addresses given by British leaders during WWII., c. 1941; DOCUMENT (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 6)
  - Testimony of gratitude to JDR from the Trustees of the Metropolitan Museum of Art for his contribution to the Medieval Collection., 1938 May; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 6)
  - Certificate from the Cleveland Museum of Art electing JDR, Jr. as endowment fellow of Board of Trustees., 1938 December 19; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Council of New York City Annual Award for Distinguished Service to the Community in 1946, presented to JDR, Jr. Citation in booklet with accompanying press clippings., 1947 May 13; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 6)
  - Award from The University Club, acknowledging JDR, Jr.'s "academic mellowness.", 1951 March 29; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 7)
  - Certificate from the NY Chamber of Commerce electing JDR, Jr. as an honorary member., 1950 April 6; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 7)
  - Certificate of appreciation presented to JDR, Jr. by Cleveland Chamber of Commerce., 1948 April 20; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 7)
  - Resolution of the NY Chamber of Commerce commending JDR, Jr. for his contributions to United Nations of their building site in Manhattan., 1947 January 9; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 7)
  - Member certificate certifying JDR, Jr. as member of George Washington Carver Endowment Fund Association., 1943 July 13; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 8, Folder 7)